Welcome to The Test Set. Here we talk with some of the brightest thinkers and tinkerers
in statistical analysis, scientific computing, and machine learning. Digging into what makes
them tick, plus the insights, experiments, and OMG moments that shape the field.
Michael's traveling at the moment, so you're stuck with a producer's voiceover this week.
On this episode, The Test Set crew jams with Caitlin Colgrove, CTO and co-founder of HEX,
the data platform that somehow counts a sweet green head chef among its power users.
Caitlin joins Michael, Padley, and Isabel to make the case that data teams aren't going
anywhere. But right now, their job is changing from writing SQL to vouching for the answers.
We hope you enjoy.
Caitlin, welcome to The Test Set.
Thank you.
Thanks for coming on. Just by way of introduction, you're Caitlin Colgrove, the CTO of HEX.
And I'm Michael Chow. I'm the host of The Test Set. And I'm joined by Hadley Wickham,
chief scientist at Posit, and Isabel, software engineer extraordinaire at Posit. And we're
so excited to have you on.
I feel like HEX is everywhere today, and I'm constantly trying to explain to people what
HEX is and why they should use it. I know HEX is included in cloud.ai now. Maybe do
you mind just explaining a little bit about what HEX is and what it does?
Yeah, totally. HEX started when we started as founders. We were basically, we'd all left
Palantir and we're kind of out in the world looking at how people were working with data.
And what we discovered was that there were a lot of new patterns for working with data
that were emerging. People were a lot more technical. There was a lot less clicking of
buttons and a lot more writing of code, SQL, Python, all of that. And the tools out there
were Jupyter notebooks. Those are very popular. This is 2019 or so. But in order to actually
sort of string together a full enterprise data workflow, like to actually do something
useful with your data, people would be doing these ad hoc analyses in Python, SQL, do
a SQL in a notebook. You still had to do the backticks. It was like really not native.
And then that was in a notebook and it was a locally running notebook with your own Python
environment. And okay, so maybe you do this whole analysis and what are you going to do?
Are you going to email that notebook to the CFO? That, you can't do that. So they would
take these notebooks and they would, okay, they're like, okay, we're going to turn it
into a Python script and then we're going to run the Python script on a schedule on
AWS. And then we're going to dump the output into Looker so that the CFO can look at it
in Looker so that they can take a screenshot of the chart and put it in the board deck.
And that was the workflow. And so Hex was really born of this idea that there just has
to be a better way, that there needs to be first-class tooling for this new era of data
work. And that was the original product that we built. And then obviously like, you know,
in the past couple of years, AI has become a huge part of that. And I think even though
some of the technology has changed, the underlying story is still true. It's people who are working
with day in and day out. What are their workflows? What are the best tools for them? And Hex
should be that.
I've seen so many engineers in Python use like Pandas read SQL, that classic, like Pandas
dot read SQL with a string of SQL in it, which feels like maybe a little bit unnatural.
More than a little bit unnatural.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. And that scheduling dynamic, just all these bits of duct tape
kind of like in the process. I'm really curious, I know like with the anthropic integration,
like what does that look like for a person to use Hex?
Yeah, so I think this is one of the big ways that work is changing. Pre-AI, you basically
had these big heavyweight vertical SAS tools. And depending on what you wanted to do, you
would navigate to HubSpot or you would navigate to Salesforce or you would navigate to Hex
because you're like, I want to do something with my marketing data. I want to do data
science, data analysis. And that would be where you would start. And so you'd have these
big full featured front doors to these vertical applications.
Today, everybody just starts by like asking Claude or ChatGPT a question. And we've actually
had some really, really interesting conversations with the Anthropic team and the OpenAI teams
about how they're seeing the changing and sort of the emergence of these new workflows.
And they really view a lot of these chat applications as a front door. They're not going to go and
build a first class data science agent or a first class customer service agent or all
of these things. They want to be the platforms on which those things run. But still today,
it's very sticky, these habits of just ask your question to Claude.
And so what Anthropic released, and ChatGPT has sort of its own version as well, is this
plugin architecture. And it's based on MCP, as you might imagine, but they've enhanced
that with more UX around it. So now if you hook up your MCP to Claude, you actually get
a interactive Hex experience in Claude. And Claude, you know, the models are actually
smart enough to know how to route. So if you go and you have Hex wired up as your sort
of data science backend, and you ask a question, Claude knows that the Hex plugin is the plugin
to use to answer that. And so it'll actually go and it'll go kick off sort of a sub-agent
architecture where it kicks off an agent in Hex, which will go look at all your data.
It'll go look at all your semantic models. It'll do all this stuff and it'll come back.
And it's actually really nice. You get to sort of see the thinking tokens. You can get
an interactive set of charts back. And then if you really want to go deep, or you want
to go build a dashboard, or you want to do something further, you can kind of click through
into the underlying Hex project that it's been building up behind the scenes.
What's a question I could ask that might produce a Hex widget? Like if I wanted to check the
weather in different cities, or like, let's say we just had, yeah, like...
What's something you have used Hex to answer about Hex?
Well today, so Hex is typically most useful for the types of enterprise data workflows
where it's all governed in the data warehouse. You've probably done some modeling on top
of it. You probably have some dashboards, you know, maybe you have your KPI dashboards
or whatever. It's like sort of classic data workflows. And then you can start to pull
in other sources, obviously via MCP and other things. But it's very similar to, you know,
like, you know, pre-AI, the types of things that you'd be managing with dbt and Snowflake
and all those things. So it's usually business data. And if you're syncing other sources,
those are to enhance the questions that you're asking about the business data. So these days,
I'm asking a lot of questions about how much we're spending on Anthropic. Where are those
tokens coming from? How are people using these products? And so that's a very, it's a sort
of, I would call a combination kind of finance product analytics type workflows. And so basically
what we're doing is we're piping all of our logging around the usage of Hex's AI into
Snowflake and all of those like fine grained token counting and, you know, attribution
and where those are coming from. And so I'm spending a lot of time looking at, you know,
where are we spending the most tokens? Are there places where we could be being more
efficient? We also have a lot of data around, you know, our internal evals and performance.
And so are there areas where we like should be using Opus and we can't actually drop down
to something like Sonnet or Haiku? So I spent a lot of time looking at that in Hex.
We know that like models can be like pretty sycophantic. Like how much do you worry about
like when you come in with a question and there's like an sort of an answer that like you want to
hear? And then like the, you know, do you worry about you kind of accidentally steering the model
in that direction that just reinforces like what you want to hear? Yeah, I think, I think that's
actually one of the bigger problems, like model behavior is one of the bigger problems in sort of
agentic AI for data science today. And it's a combination of that. It's, it's, I think it's
a less of the sycophancy side of things that we see, but we see a lot of confidently incorrect.
So the models will, instead of doing what even a relatively junior data scientist would do,
which is you start looking at the data, you start exploring, you get an answer, and then you
check that answer. Maybe you look at some other, you know, sort of other sources to see if you can
corroborate what you're seeing. Models don't do that at all. They find a table, they're like, ah,
this table has a column that looks like it should be useful, and then they just go. And so that's
one thing that we're thinking a lot about is like how do we give the models, how do we push them to
explore the space more? And how do we push them to sort of self-validate in, in a way that more
likely will, because often, and you see this even with humans, right? If, if you start at different
points in the data and there's different ways and different assumptions that you might make about
how to answer a question, you can end up with just wildly different answers. And you kind of want to
look at all of those and understand, okay, well, what's, what's the actual sort of truth here?
There's a lot of knobs to turn when making sure that the model is, you know,
being a little bit more creative, maybe thinking a little bit harder about the answers.
What are maybe the knobs that you're thinking about in HEX to make sure that this is being
solved? Yeah, I think the models these days are very, they're, the reasoning steps are actually
quite good and quite solid. And it, you know, if you rewind a couple of years and hallucinations
and just like them not paying attention to the things that you want them to pay attention to
are huge, huge problems. And even just keeping them on task. These days, I actually find that
they're quite creative in taking the pieces of information that they have and putting them
together into an answer. Like that's actually, it's actually like really impressive when you
read their thinking traces, how much they're able to like hit a roadblock and overcome it and like
cycle through that in order to get to an answer. Where I usually see the problems happening is,
as I was saying before, in them having not sufficiently explored the space. And so they're
very, very good at coming up with an answer based on what they have, but if they don't have all of
the pieces that you need them to have, then that's where they'll, you know, that's where
they'll kind of fall on their face. They may even have an answer that looks plausible, but it's
actually not, not what you want. Or maybe they'll, you know, they won't, they won't even get to an
answer. So where we, what we're thinking about is that exploration phase. And you, and you see this
in, in other modes too, like in coding, you have like a, kind of have like a plan and design phase
and then an implementation phase. That's something that we're thinking about how we bake into our
models where you don't necessarily just like start from the question and have them go at it.
You actually kind of push them to look harder for things before they come back and start to
actually then go and do the analysis. Just to be sure, I'm, I'm going to try to paint
in exquisite detail what it looks like to use Hex just because it's, it's such an interesting,
cool experience. But I also think some people, when I talk to people, some people listening,
I think might have trouble if you've never used Hex, like just conveying it that, and correct me
for anything I get wrong, but if I understand, it's kind of like you have often like data in
the warehouse and say like an analytics engineer, or some people have tried to transform and kind of
curate what you need. And you might even be a person who doesn't do a ton of data analysis.
You know, you might be working in like finance or not, no shade on finance or like another area
and essentially you go into this notebook that's wired up to your warehouse. And right now you're
able to ask an agent essentially a question. And then what happens is it starts populating cells
that run and produce outputs. And some of these outputs even are like filters. So it might be like
a dropdown to select like something you're interested in, or to filter a company that
you might want data on. And then essentially like you can adjust the filter and everything
else in the notebook will kind of update. So you can sort of like build this notebook and explore
your data at the same time. But then what I think is also interesting that I just want to make sure
to mention is, if I understand you also have an app mode, is that right? Where you kind of shift
from seeing the code in the notebook view to the app mode where the code sort of like goes away or
is more hidden? Is that? Yeah. Yeah. That's all totally correct. I think you can think about it
in Hex as the backbone of the product is this notebook. And we were just chatting about this
earlier. That notebook actually under the hood is essentially a graph of transformation nodes that we
can run behind the scenes. And then you can take that notebook, which we call project in Hex,
and you can do a bunch of different things with it. So you can manipulate it with the agent. So
the agent will actually like edit that graph. It will build up that graph. And you can do that,
you know, just to do sort of some exploratory analysis. But often what you want and often,
and this is actually one of the huge pain points that Hex was solving in the early days is,
you know, data workflows don't end with getting a number. They end with making a business decision.
And so the way you get from, I have an answer from the data to we've actually decided to do
something. There has to be sort of a collaboration and presentation and sharing step. And so what
we've done with Hex, it used to be excruciatingly difficult to go from those analyses to that,
you know, screenshotting charts into PowerPoint and things like that. And so what we've done is
we've actually layered a presentation layer directly on top of the notebook. So it's exactly
the same. And, you know, it's a typical more dashboard like experience, I would say. We call
them apps because they can be more powerful under the hood than what you would expect from a
traditional dashboard. And then you can also really extend this. So this has actually like
been such a versatile paradigm for us. So Hex has the notebook and the notebook agent, which is
really geared towards technical people. It's people who want to be in the code, even if the
agent's writing it, they want to be looking at it and working with it. But there's a lot of people
in the organization who don't want to look at the code, but also still want to be able to take
advantage of the power of the Hex agent. And so what we have is we have our conversational agent,
which we call threats. But under the hood, it's actually the same as the notebook agent.
And so what it's doing… I love it puts a different hat on.
Yeah, it's a skin. But it's actually building up a notebook behind the scenes. And this is
really, really powerful because it means that if you get to the end of this conversation and
then you want to do something with it, maybe that thing is share it. Well, great. You're in a
notebook. You can make the same types of dashboards, things like that, that you could before. Or maybe
you're like, hey, I don't know if this is right. I actually want to send it to the data team to
check my work. Well, the work's all there in the notebook behind the project.
Yeah, Hadley, I know you… In R, it's super different, right? Like the analysis, the kind of
workflow versus a notebook where you're sort of like, this workflow is so great. If I'm
understanding, it's kind of like, whoops, I made a dashboard. You do your notebook stuff,
but then you have a dashboard at the end. Yeah, I think it's really interesting because
the sort of heritage of R is this like REPL, this run, eval, print loop where you're in the
console trying stuff out. And that's kind of your primary means of exploration and experimentation.
And then as you discover things, you kind of believe to be true. Like that's when you record
them into a script. And that's kind of what led to R Mark down on Korto, which is like,
you've written this mingling of pros and code, like much like a notebook, but you then you run
the whole thing and that produces your output. And that has some like big advantages, like kind of
pre-reactive notebooks, very easy in a Jupyter notebook to kind of get into this state where
you've like run some cells in like different orders and there's no way to reproduce what
you've done. Like no way to have that problem with R Mark down because you always run it from scratch.
Like there's a different set of problems, obviously a different set of trade-offs,
but like that's the one problem you never experience. And then I guess there's often
a dashboard phase after. Yeah. And so the thing that you produce might be a document,
it might be a dashboard, it might be a presentation. Like I think that that same like
underlying thing and you're putting on like different hats for different people. That's
just, that's like such a valuable metaphor. I mean, we kind of often joke in engineering,
I guess, like, Oh, that's a DAG. That's a directed acyclic graph. Like everything's,
Oh, that's an immutable DAG. That's a reactive DAG. Like, Oh, wow. What a surprise. Like we've
created a DAG and it turns out to be the right model. It's just. And sometimes so at, obviously
the hex notebook, as we've been talking about behind the scenes is DAG. And as the, as the
cells within the notebook got more and more complicated, we started to realize that the
cells themselves needed to be DAG. And so then you have DAGs and DAGs and DAGs, it's DAGs all
the way down. And actually, you know, what is a DAG of DAGs? It's just a DAG. Yeah. It's kind of
like every, it feels like every problem with an LLM you solve with like another LLM, like,
you don't know if your LLM is doing a good job or not. Well, let's have an LLM, a different LLM
judge whether it's doing a good job. And it's, yeah, it's like turtles all the way down.
And another thing, just, just to not to keep buttering up Hex, but OpenAI, they released
their, one of their reports was using Hex. Is that right? Like a state of data?
Uh, probably Anthropic. Anthropic. Okay. Yes. I gotta be careful about mine. Yeah. Do you recall
what that was? There was like a... I don't know specifically what you're referring to. There's a,
there's a few times where we've seen Anthropic kind of use Hex in there. It like pops up. Yeah.
Because, you know, they're, they're Hex customers. Yeah. And sometimes it's fun to like watch their
live streams and like spot the Hex charts. Yeah. Yeah. For Hex. Yeah. Yeah. That's cool.
And I know, I know you mentioned, um, Sweetgreen as an example.
Oh yeah. This is a recent one. Um, Hex, Hex is like the whole spectrum of customers. You know,
it's like very traditional data science all the way to some of these use cases that you would just
never imagine. Um, so Sweetgreen just signed on as a Hex customer and this was the wildest one
that I've, I've heard in a while. They use Hex to monitor the temperature of their ovens so that
they can correlate customer complaints about the temperature of their food to, you know,
what's happening on the ground in their restaurants. It was wild. Every now and then you come up with,
you hear some of these things from customers. It's actually one of the really fun things about
building a product that's so flexible and so horizontal. Did the head chef have like a lot
of data experience? Like what's... You know, I'm not, I'm not sure. Um, I, you know, I,
I actually haven't met him, him personally, but this is one that we heard kind of from our field
teams. Yeah. Like one of the things I've sort of been, you know, thinking about like how,
like as these, you know, people who never would have, you know, worked with data in this way
before, cause they couldn't program like, and now they can because they can write in English.
But, you know, there's a lot of like vocab and like ways of thinking about data that you don't,
you, you don't have and you can't express in everyday English. Like how do we start to like
train those people up to give them like the basic kind of like that kind of gut feel for like,
I should be a little bit skeptical here or like, Oh, what I, what I need right now is like a smooth
or like I need to tidy data or how do you all think about that? Yeah. So I think this is an
unsolved problem broadly. Um, and that I think building these agents to behave like a data
scientist, um, truly, I think we haven't gotten there yet and there's a lot more work to be done
there, but I actually think that this is one of the big breakthroughs broadly in terms of, um, uh,
you know, AI for data and really enabling a much broader spectrum of people to work with data
because yes, there's, you know, the actual, can you write code aspect of it? But if you look at
sort of the prior generation of data tools, even ones where you don't have to write any code,
people still don't use them. Um, like the lay people in the organization do not use them. Like
we talked to a Looker, uh, an ex Looker customer, another hex customer. And they said, you know,
they bought Looker for everybody. And in practice it was like, they looked at the last 90 days and
only two people in the company had made like new dashboards in London. Um, and when you like unpack
that a little bit, it's just buttons, right? You don't have to write code. How hard can it be?
It's actually that doing data work is just inherently very complex. Um, and so none of
these tools code or otherwise, uh, more walkup usable. There was just too much foundational
knowledge that you needed in order to be able to be effective in the tool. And so one of the
big breakthroughs besides the, you know, LLM writing code bit is actually imbuing the agents
with that knowledge. Um, and today that's already a lot of what we're doing with the hex agent is
like teaching it, not just like, you know, how to write code, but you know, how to work with the
data, you know, the, your tribal knowledge around the organization of what data is where all of
those things you bake into the agents. Um, and so you're starting to see this pattern across, you
know, across agents in general purpose, uh, models with skills and things like that. Again, I don't
think we've totally nailed it because I think even with a skill, um, some of these more specialized
domains like data and data science, the models haven't been post-trained on it as, you know,
as rigorously as I have been with coding. I think there's like a, you know, still a fair
amount of headroom, but it's like, even if it's, you know, 60, 70%, it's still massively better
than someone who's never really thought about how to work with data before. So our internally at
hex, some of our, we have, we have this feature that we call guides, which is basically basically
skills. Um, and some of them are like, you know, this is how this data set is shaped and things
like that. And some of them are, you know, this is how we do data analysis at hex. These are the
types of things that you should do. Um, and the models are pretty good at adhering to it today.
But again, as we've been talking about, if there's any kind of like judgment or anything
that they would need to off-road on that, that they're like much, much less good at.
It is. And like, I think one of the things a good data scientist has always done, like
you come with a question and then the data scientists like helps you turn that into a
question that you can actually answer, like with the data you have. And like, you know,
if you just go into the data warehouse and you just start asking questions, you're like, you,
you just don't even know like the right questions to ask. And that's such a valuable kind of,
and we're starting to get that a little bit with LLMs, I think they can at least help you
brainstorm and kind of say, Oh, Hey, you could ask this instead. But yeah, it's, it's, it's
interesting, interesting time to be a data scientist. The other thing that we do in Hex
that I think is very powerful, um, is the agents have access to not just the underlying data
warehouse, but the other things that people are doing with the data. Um, and so some of
this is going to be garbage, just like, you know, people not knowing what they're doing,
but, um, you know, you may have that company dashboard that gets looked at, you know,
thousands of times a day or whatever. And that is actually a very rich source of context for the
agent for how you should do something. And so when a user comes in, it's like,
I want to know something about revenue. They may not know anything about how we actually
calculate revenue, but that's actually encoded in various places in your data workspace that
the agent, which is, yeah, which is because I mean, that's also how humans work, right?
Often that's not documented. You have to go to another successful project and like copy and
paste that code. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That was an interesting point. I think I saw a poster
recently. It was like this idea of maybe like some of your best documentation is just the other
projects around and that the agents it's, if I understand y'all made it so the agent can
essentially like look across projects so that if it doesn't exist, like in the documentation or in
the models, it can sort of figure out how someone else maybe like went off road or use some kind of
like knowledge in their head, um, to do something. Yeah, exactly. I mean, the idea here is it's
always been extremely difficult and basically impossible for humans to exhaustively and
thoroughly document their entire data ecosystem and then maintain that and keep that, keep them
up to date. So what are the other places that you can go to understand, um, you know, how to use
particular parts of data or how to do particular types of analyses. And, you know, it's, it's a
range because when you have, when you have the documented context, um, for the most part, that's
like highly trusted and that's something that the agents can just rely on. But then everything else
is this range from, you could go all the way down from like, oh, I'm just going to like look at the
SQL queries that were executed against this table all the way up to, um, you know, you have a project
that, you know, is highly used and maintained by the data team. And in Hex you, we have this mode
called endorsements where basically the data team can put a tag on it. That's like, this is like a
blessed gold star. Yeah. Essentially. Yes. And all of this is to help guide the agent towards,
you want it, you want it to be able to take advantage of all the context that it's
able to, but you also want it to be able to distinguish between the highly trusted
parts and then the less trusted parts. Cause I think that that is like one of the risks of
agents because they can be so much more productive. You just get stuck in this loop where they kind of
get worse and worse and worse and a greater and greater purdue proportion of your internal
dashboards and stuff are written by agents and they're just learning from other agents who made
mistakes like 15 months ago. And yeah, like that, that kind of idea of saying like, we also need to
give feedback. Like these are the really good things that like copy from that, not from.
And, and this I think is one of the key sort of new jobs to be done for the data teams,
if that makes sense. Um, and a big part of, of Hex that we haven't really talked about yet,
but is relatively new, um, post agent is what we call the context studio, which is basically about
observability and management of all of the context for all of the agents.
And so you can see what people, you know, what the agents are actually doing for each thread. You can
actually see what context the agent is using. And then we have a second, uh, sort of like a separate
set of agentic workflows around managing the context around extracting the pieces out of these
things. Um, and then putting that, feeding that back into the like highly trusted, highly governed
context to kind of avoid this like spiraling problem of, you know, the agent just kind of
deciding that that's the way to do something. And then that producing, um, sort of being a
self-fulfilling prophecy over there, you can actually like break that. You can see that
it's actually doing something that's, that's incorrect. Um, and then update your human
managed context, um, which is prioritized, you know, more highly above the kind of ambient context
for the agents. I'm really curious. I read recently that now more agents are deploying
code on Hex than humans. Um, how do you manage as someone who obviously cares so much about their
users and like is giving people such a beautiful suite of tools, like what are you making for
agents versus what are you making for people nowadays? Yeah, it's a really good question. I
think in the early days of building the Hex agent, it was very clear that, um, the tools that we'd
built for humans were actually also very good for agents. And so there was a lot of overlap. Um,
you know, we had this modular notebook structure, looks a lot like tools that you can give to the
agent. Um, and the agents just took to that very naturally. And that was like the first
generation I would say, where it was pretty, pretty one-to-one. But now that we've had this
sort of crossover moment, um, of more code is being written in Hex by agents than by,
than by people, you start to think about what that implies for the rest of the system. And
you still have, you still want the human interfaces because there are still times
where people are going to come in and tweak things. And, you know, it's, it's not, it's not
fully, fully, um, be a natural language. Like sometimes typing a whole sentence is just a very
inefficient way to do something that's, you know, as opposed to clicking a button.
typing a whole sentence is just a very inefficient way to do something, as opposed to clicking
a button. But at the same time, knowing that over time, more and more of this is going
to get produced by agents, it actually gives you a lot of opportunities to build things
that are useful for agents, but less useful for humans, but are very powerful for the
agents. And so, you know, one thing that we've thought about in HEX is, could we give the
agents slightly different — all of our cells are built to be, you know, they're very sort
of easy to inspect, you get a little preview, you get all of these nice UI features.
are very easy to inspect, you get a little preview, you get all of these nice UI features.
Agents don't need that.
And actually, they're quite expensive.
So if an agent is building up a project, could you give it a slightly different set of tools
that would have different characteristics?
Maybe less data warehouse load, maybe it runs faster.
Maybe it's just, honestly, sometimes agents like to work in a different way than humans.
They've been trained on a certain distribution of data, and it's not exactly what our human
brains have been trained on.
And so I do think that there will be some divergence there.
But the power of HECS is that these things are shared across — they're interoperable.
And I think that will continue to be true for a while.
One of the things I really like about the context studio is it feels like HECS is sort
of thinking, well, your job of what a data team or data science do is changing.
This is going to be one of the things where you give value to your organization, as opposed
to like there's also a lot of startups out there today, which their pitch is basically
like buy us and fire your data team, which, you know, as a data scientist doesn't feel
very nice.
Well, we were talking to a head of data, and he said something that was really interesting.
And I think when you frame it in this way, it made it really clear to me why data teams
are not going away.
He said, my job is to vouch for the correctness of the data and the answer that you get.
He's the head of the data team, and obviously that's a slightly different role than ICs on
the data team.
But when you frame it like that, you're like, oh, yeah, actually, in the abstract, when
you don't have people clicking buttons, that is the job of the data team.
The job of the data team is to make a system that produces correct answers.
And today, a lot of that has to do with, instead of being the person who writes the sequel
that is correct, it doesn't have bugs in it, how do you set up the context layer such that
the agents can arrive there themselves?
Yeah.
I mean, the depressing thing is, definitely in corporate America, having the person to
fire when something goes wrong is important.
I mean, even more positively, someone has to own the stuff and be like, yeah, it's my
reputation on the line that this is correct.
You can't just distribute that to a bunch of nebulous agents that no one really understands.
Yeah.
Ownership is not just like, it's my reputation on the line, but it's like, you know, my job
is to make sure that this functions.
And because it's, you know, in organizations like this data is being used for, you know,
existential, answering existential questions, like the business needs someone to care that
that is correct and to, you know, build the system that is correct, rather than just kind
of assuming that everything's gonna be fine and figure it out.
Yeah.
But it does feel like data teams are going to get more unhinged analysis from execs.
That's also going to have to be part of their job.
Someone has done something that they think is really cool, and it is really cool that
more people in the org are interacting directly with the data.
But the consequence of that is more people are going to be making mistakes and the data
team is going to have to walk them back.
Yeah.
You already see this.
You see this in software engineering, like, you know, a CEO will come in and like, you
know, use cursor or whatever to like vibe code some insane thing and then like make
a pull request because like all the like traditional barriers to that happening.
And then, you know, the engineers are kept to code and like review this thing.
I do think you'll start to see a similar pattern like that in data where all of a sudden people
have all of these really powerful tools at their fingertips and they don't know how to
use them.
And I think there's a couple of things there.
One is, you know, in HEX, we're thinking a lot about building review tools, both, you
know, manual and also agent assisted review tools so that that process is as painless
as possible.
But I also think it's just another indication of, you know, where there will still be value.
Like there are there are times where you actually want an expert to do the analysis.
There's many, many ways to do the wrong things with statistics.
And if you if you have a very important decision, there will still be a time and a place for
people to kind of do those things and not just have someone, you know, fire off an agent
query and and, you know, not not be able to really think critically about the result they're
getting.
It's funny you say that because our CEO got in trouble with our IT department for an app
he vibe coded with HR.
I think it's so like maybe empowering and lovely to think about, you know, data scientists
are coming with all of the the muscles for, you know, really productive AI usage like
data scientists do a lot of experiments.
Data scientists know you look at something, say, wow, this is bad.
Like let's scrap it all and start again.
So I think there's something really interesting and especially with the aid of things like
review tools built in the loop, you know, no better time question mark to be someone
who's writing code to do data science.
Yeah.
And I think there's a lot of hype around AI engineering and things like that.
And we internally at Hex have an AI engineering team.
One thing that I've observed is sort of the lines between our AI engineering team and
our data team really blurring and starting to overlap.
And so, for example, a lot of things that we'll do internally for our ourselves to build
our own product and build our own agent, we'll build, you know, we have evals, we have various
other things that we've built.
You know, we will look at those and be like, oh, we should actually take those and put
those into the product for our customers.
Because these workflows of, you know, building a highly trusted agent actually, you know,
converge over time.
Yeah.
Who runs Hex's internal context studio?
Who's the person curating that?
Yeah.
That's our data team.
Nice.
Yeah.
And they are like our number one dog fooders.
For obvious reasons.
Yeah.
Do you see like the lines blurring elsewhere?
Not just because, I guess like in our, like we're starting to see like designers who previously
would create, you know, like a beautiful thing and turn it over to engineers to implement.
Now they can give a work, deliver a working prototype or like product people who previous
were like, hey engineer, can you implement this?
They just go away and do that.
Like are you seeing that blurring of lines in your engineering work too?
I would say absolutely.
But I think it's a little bit less dramatic at Hex than maybe at other places because
our org has always kind of been designed like this, if that makes sense.
Most of our PMs used to be technical, like actually hands-on technical in some capacity.
All of our designers, we like give them an interview that's designed to be like, can
you do light, you know, CSS and React work?
Like we don't want people to just be completely boxed out of a core part of the technology.
You know, our front end engineers and our backend engineers kind of flow back and forth.
Everybody has their spikes, you know, it's not like we're expecting, you know, a backend
engineer to be, you know, deep in React.
But we don't want people to have these really hard boundaries because that can often create
just like a lot of really annoying inefficiencies in the organization.
And so, yes, we are seeing that blur.
We're sort of seeing that intensify, I would say, like, you know, designers and product
managers are like, can go much deeper kind of in what they're able to contribute than
they used to be.
But, you know, we hired a lot of people who are excited about that.
So I think that's like just strictly a good thing.
Yeah, it's interesting.
And maybe this is a nice segue into a less kind of AI, more style topic.
But Hex has incredible style.
Hex is just cool.
I don't know how to explain, like, you go to the Hex website, and it's been like this
for years and years and years, I feel like.
The website, cool.
The booths at conferences, unhinged.
In a good way.
I'm sorry.
Like a retro dining booth.
Hex is throwing like magic shows.
I don't know how to ask this.
How did Hex acquire such immaculate style?
Well, I'm going to have to give some credit to some other people in the organization for
that one.
My co-founder, Barry, the second person we ever hired was Adam, our head of design.
And I think, you know, those two have been kind of the masterminds.
So Annie, our head of brand design, have been the masterminds of a lot of these things.
So in some ways, it's down to specific individuals and having particular individuals who have
these kind of off-the-wall takes.
But I think also it's about the culture that you build as an organization and who you find
and us trying to bring in people who are creative, who don't take themselves too seriously.
And when you have some of those things, it creates an environment where you can be generative
and think differently like this.
And yeah, so it's both.
There's like some very, very talented people that we have and also, you know, the team
that we built around them.
Yeah.
I really like the Hex.
Like the Hex color scheme is like so, like it really stands out and like tick.
No one is like pink and cream and brown.
Like that's, I mean, probably now that's the next trend, but like, you know, I kind of
love, like we spent a lot of effort at Posit coming up with our logo and stuff, but just
like blue and orange is just like such a like traditional kind of tech color scheme.
It's yeah.
It's just fascinating to see like as we grow as a company, how these kind of forces of
like unification and kind of corporatization, like pull on you towards these, just like
this is like the safe, safe choice.
And yeah, and some of that just has to do with, you have to scale your content and branding
engine.
And so early on, a lot of creativity can actually just come from particular individuals.
And you almost always get certainly a more like unique results when you're, when you're
doing that and you're doing that in small teams.
And then you get to a point where it's like, oh, you have to write all of this content
and you have to put out things on Twitter and LinkedIn to get the, you know, SEO or
AEO or whatever we're doing now.
And you just, the amount of stuff that you have to produce can't bottleneck through your
main creative engines.
And sometimes you can scale, like you obviously scale your brand voice and your brand styling
and things like that, but you can't do it perfectly.
And so I do think that, you know, we're, we're trying to fight really hard against this and
trying to like balance the two, but you do sometimes sort of inevitably have feel this
like regression towards the mean pole, just like the more and more stuff you have to do
on the branding side.
Yeah.
And it's sort of also interesting just as the company grows, like the, the amount of
visibility you have within all of the parts of the organization.
And this like sounds weird coming from a data person, but like you are forced to start developing
like metrics so that you can get some oversight and then like metrics are good, obviously,
but they're also bad because they kind of like trap you into these like predefined,
like how, like how do you like wrestle with that as like clearly a data driven company,
but you don't want to be like too data driven at the same time.
Yeah.
I think for me, a lot of it, a lot of it has come down to being able to sort of shift the
altitude at which you operate and then knowing when is the right time to be at what altitude.
So obviously it's extremely important, you know, as a senior leader of a company to be
thinking about strategy and long-term time horizons.
And I spend a lot of time, obviously we spend a lot of time talking about AI.
Our AI strategy is where I spend a lot of my time thinking.
And then, you know, you're intermediated through layers and layers of organization.
And sometimes there's something down at the bottom that's like not going well.
And if you've built a good organization, you'll know about that most of the time, but sometimes
you don't.
And sometimes you just, you see things in the data or you see things, you know, that
don't feel right.
And I think for me, cultivating that kind of like instinct of, hey, this section feels
like it feels like there's something not working here.
The vibes are off.
And being able to just do a deep dive on that.
And in order to be able to do that, you have to know enough about the things that are like
happening on the ground.
And so for me, you know, when I first started really building up a bunch of our AI programs,
I spent, and I still do actually, like I read the papers, like I spent a bunch of time
in the technology and that's to both to like be able to see the big picture, but also when
something's not right on the ground, to be able to kind of go all the way down and like
help debug, you know, where something is breaking down.
Yeah.
As CTO of Hex, I'm so curious, what is your, what does that look like?
Like what's your day to day look like?
It's a pretty big range of things.
I think one of the funny things about being CTO is sometimes I feel like my job is more
about humans than it is about technology, even though technology is in the title.
And so a lot of it is about what I'm not sort of thinking about the AI side of the AI technology
side of things.
A lot of it is about like, how, how are we running a functional technology organization?
And there's engineering, there's data, there's, there's our survey, our research side, there's
security, there's all of these things involved in that.
And a lot of that day to day is actually not necessarily like making technology decisions.
Like I've hired smart people, if I've done my, especially in areas like security where
I'm not the expert, if I've done my job right, I've hired people who are better at making
those technology decisions than I am.
It's about, you know, setting up the humans to do their best work.
But as someone who's like come up from the kind of technologic, like the technical side,
like how do you, like, do you still, is there some amount of programming like you just want
to do to kind of like scratch that internal itch of like being?
Let me cook.
Yeah.
Yeah, for sure.
A lot of it I try to do on sort of side, less, you know, mission critical, critical path
things right now.
Some of it is actually fun to get.
So when I was in college, my concentration was, was on called ML.
And then I did my master's in NLP.
And so I've always really been interested in this side of the house, but this was over
10 years ago.
For people who might not know, NLP is natural language processing.
And it's all about.
It's basically all of, it's like pre LLMs, pre generative AI, how you operated with natural
language in, you know, in a statistical sort of modeling sense.
And actually a lot of the techniques back when I was in college were sort of hilariously
primitive versions of what we have today, if that makes sense.
So, but, you know, it was, it was pretty clear, this was 2012, it was pretty clear
that this was like the stuff that they were doing was like kind of neat and you could
like see some interesting properties of language with it.
But like your ability, you couldn't generate text, like your, your ability to actually
do things like machine translation was like a big area of study back then.
And it was like, you know, comically bad, you know, it was like, you could get the gist
of what the, what the text was saying, but it wasn't anywhere approximating real speech.
And it was pretty clear to me that like the techniques that we were learning about as
state-of-the-art at the time were like, not it.
And so I kind of like left that and went into just core software engineering because I was
like, I want to do something real.
I want to do something that's like practical.
And then sure enough, a few years later, Attention Was All You Need was published and it's kind
of like off to the races from there.
But so, so, so sometimes it's me getting hands-on and building things.
And sometimes it's me just like getting back into that has been really fun and spending
some time, not just like reading blogs, but like reading the actual underlying papers
and like understanding, understanding the research side has been, has been like super
fun over the last couple of years.
Yeah.
Oh, that's interesting.
So you've been kind of diving back into NLP.
It kind of like reignited.
Yeah.
I mean, well now, now it's just, you know, all generative AI and it's like, it's sort
of a blurred line.
Large language models do so many more things other than just NLP.
But yeah, a lot of, a lot of it is like, again, at the foundational level, like, you know,
similar techniques.
It's all just matrix multiplication under the hood anyway.
It is interesting.
Like, you know, like named, named entity recognition used to be like this really challenging thing.
You have to have a massive tech stack specifically for that.
And now you just like throw it at any random LLM and it does a good job.
If I'm a barbarian, what's named entity recognition?
Like, you know, if you've got like a blog post and you just want to extract all the
people's names that were mentioned in it, like that's, you can't do that with a regular
expression.
One of the hard problems is naming things.
Yeah.
Extracting names from things.
Like I remember, um, a very long time ago, Hilary Mason had this really cool blog post
where she scraped like 200 chocolate chip cookie recipes and then created like the average
chocolate chip cookie recipe, which she then made.
And like back then that was like, that was a lot of work.
I was like, wow, that is so cool.
And that is now something I could do today.
And you know, like 30 minutes with, or less than that, you just ask chat GPT for a chocolate
cookie recipe.
And that's basically what you're getting.
Yeah.
Ben Stancil mentioned something about this too, where like, and having to do with data
work, like support, if you have like thousands of support tickets, you know, as a data team,
you might have used to go in and tried to analyze it and maybe like calculate a number
from support tickets.
He mentioned, yeah, like nowadays you might even just dump your support tickets into like
chat GPT or something and just ask like your question directly.
Whereas before we were trying to roll up numbers to try to kind of.
Yeah.
You try to have to do some sort of like.
In between.
Yeah.
You have to like take the unstructured thing and then, you know, run some models over it,
maybe some classifiers, maybe some sentiment analysis, maybe you're like extracting specific
signal from it.
And then you get this like very, very limited structured representation of it, topic, you
know, topic clustering or whatever.
And then you like try to figure that out, figure out what's going on based on that.
And some of that actually is still very complimentary, I would say, because, you know, LLMs are non-deterministic
and they're not very precise, especially for things that are like if you're just dumping
a bunch of unstructured data into them for things that are require, you know, numerical
calculations and things like marrying those two things can be challenging.
But for things like, you know, what are the most common, you know, user complaints?
I've done this in Hex on Hex data.
And you can it's actually like very, very fast and very powerful to pull out that kind
of signal.
Yeah.
Are you saying like user complaints?
You can get surprisingly far by putting a lot of the feedback in and just asking.
Yeah.
Just get straight to the kind of where you're going.
And you probably want to move into the more structured realm when you're getting to the
point where you're like trying to be like, OK, well, what fraction of users are asking
about this?
And, you know, you know, how does that compare to like time to resolve the tickets and things
like that?
Then you probably do want to start to shift into like a more classically structured data.
Often you just want like imagine like someone with all the support tickets and they're just
going to give you the vibes like that's super useful, even if they can't tell you, like
25% support tickets are about blah.
Yeah.
I like the alternative data science workflow.
If you have this like from like R for data science, you have this workflow that's like
import, tidy, transform.
I like the alternative, which is like copy paste.
Yeah.
Just try to get to.
Just give me the vibes and then you like.
And then you can iterate.
But I think I even find that with like some of my projects where I'm just like, hey, Claude,
just Claude Code, just do this.
Like look at this transcript, do the stuff to it.
And then I'm like, OK, this this it feels like this has teeth.
And then I'm like, OK, now Claude Code, write the code that will do that for me, like reliably
and reproducibly.
Like that's such a just to be able to do that very, very quick initial prototype to say
like, is there anything here that I should bother exploring further?
You have come from, you know, co-founder, your CTO.
I'm really curious.
Like what does success look for you look like for you, especially, you know, in the age
of AI?
Maybe how has that changed throughout your career?
Yeah, I think starting a company has really forced me to like disentangle myself from
classic indicators of success, if that makes sense.
And there's a couple of reasons for that.
One is you'll just drive yourself absolutely insane.
You're like that company has how much revenue and they raised how much like you just like
you just can't compare yourself.
Like a lot of us, you know, come up through school.
You're basically like ruthlessly, you know, trained to optimize this like one metric and
like compare yourself against all the other people to get into.
And like you just have to just let all of that go.
Like you just have to let the numbers go and focus on, you know, what you can control.
And I think the other thing about being a co-founder that I found, I found that the
hardest part about being a co-founder is that you are, you know, the job changes every six
months.
And so what that means is just as you're getting your feet under you, you have to do something
different.
And so you're always in this mode of like, I'm not good at the thing I'm supposed to
be doing right now.
I'm learning how to do this.
And for someone who, you know, generally, you know, had a relatively successful career
prior to that, you're like, you're used to operating in areas where you're good and you're
strong and things that you were hard for and you interviewed well for and you're like great
at software engineering and being a co-founder is just like not like that.
And so all of these like classic ways of being like I am successful just kind of go out the
window.
And I think for me, I just kind of keep coming back to a couple of different things.
One is, are we building something that, you know, is doing good for the world?
That is a useful contribution.
And then am I enjoying what I'm doing?
Is this a good use of my time?
And as long as I feel like and, you know, you don't have to enjoy everything that you're
doing, but like sort of in the macro.
And as long as you feel like those two things are happening, then I think that's like a
pretty it's actually like it's quite rare to really be nailing both of those things.
And so that's kind of how I've been thinking about my own personal career success.
Do you feel like there was one pivot that was like this is the hardest thing or this
is the easiest thing?
Was there one pivot that felt like it hit harder than the rest?
I don't know.
I think in some ways I kind of from the beginning of Hex had to make that pivot even just to
start the company.
And it was a bit of a sort of mental hurdle to get over because prior to that, my career
had been extremely linear.
It was like I see and then manager and then manager of managers.
And then like, you know, you just kind of like walking up that and taking a step away
from that.
And and also candidly, like, you know, I went into Hex being like, I don't know if this
is going to work.
Right.
You know, most startups don't work.
We may all be back on the job market in a year or two, and that would feel like failure.
But I think getting kind of getting past that and being like, you know, is that the worst
thing in the world?
Like, we try something and it doesn't work out like maybe you're like slightly embarrassed.
I don't know.
Like, what is the actual negative outcome there?
And kind of pushing through that feeling of like, oh, what if it fails?
Well, what if it does fail?
So what?
We all go like we're all software engineers.
And I think that was probably the biggest mindset change and even just jumping off and
then, you know, having to kind of repeatedly remind myself of that over the years.
One of the frameworks I found really useful is like this idea of maximizing versus satisficing.
Like, I think I feel like, you know, data people, people have had good grades at school,
like your natural thing is to always like find the best, like maximize.
Like I find this a lot when I'm trying to like buy a hotel somewhere, like I do so much
comparison shopping, because I'm trying to find like the best combination of location
and price.
Hotel medicine.
Exactly.
Whereas the alternative approach of like satisficing of just finding the first thing that's going
to be like good enough.
Like, that's such a powerful like mindset change.
Like you don't have to be like, not everything in your life has to be the best.
Just like finding the things that like make you where you'll be like happy and satisfied.
There's an interesting story of like the, you know, step one to two feels hard, but
what was way harder was step zero to one.
And you know, what, what mindset shifts do you have to do to even get to a spot where
you're at zero versus, you know, continuing to just go like, oh, well, I'm at one, I can
go to two, I can go to three.
It's like the same with like growing a team, like the first person, like going from zero
to one is really hard.
And one to two, that's not so bad.
And then it just gets kind of get on the downhill slope a little bit.
Yeah.
This is a pretty common piece of coaching that I give to engineers, which is, it's basically
telling them, like giving them permission not to be miserable.
I love that.
Yeah.
They, they, they often, sometimes in engineering, sometimes again, sometimes you got to do what
you got to do.
You know, sometimes someone like we had an engineer who moved into an engineering manager
role and was miserable.
They hated it.
And I was like, you can go back.
Like we actually intentionally have set up our work structure such that like senior engineer
and engineering manager are the same, no pay difference.
They're just the same level, just a different title, different role.
And coaching people through their first moment of, I tried it and I didn't like it.
And I didn't like make it all the way to something that feels like a success moment, but that's
okay.
I don't have to get there.
If I'm really unhappy with what I'm doing, I can just stop.
And that, especially like we've been talking about for people, high achievers that can
feel like a failure because sometimes you're in a, you're in a spot where you're actually
not doing a great job at the thing that you're supposed to be doing.
And you feel like you have to push through to get to a point where like you've made it,
but I don't know.
We only, you only live once, right?
Like, you know what you do with your time matters.
And there's only a certain amount of like pushing through.
And it really depends on like what the underlying reason is that you're not happy.
There's like lots of different reasons, but usually I see this in a case where someone
just like, they don't like the role.
And that's not a failure.
That's just like, you would rather be doing something different.
Obviously like there's differences where, you know, you just have, sometimes you do
have to power through like tough times in the company and you just have to like make
it out the other side.
But those are temporary things.
Like the role doesn't change.
The role is still the role.
And so if you don't like it, don't do it.
You mentioned like the kind of uncertainty of starting a startup reflected in this person's
shift to engineering manager.
You mentioned, you know, the fear of starting a startup and thinking like, what if it fails?
And then being able to say like, so what?
Like I tried it and I'll still have other things to work on.
I'll have learned and grow.
I think that like mindset shift between like this experiment failed versus I'm a failure.
Like that's a really, really big difference.
And to coach an engineer on that, that like jumping from to being an engineering manager
is a similar like experiment as starting a company.
Does it make sense for that person?
Maybe it is probably as big and as scary of a jump I'd imagine to try this like new way
of operating and that you might not know how you'll do.
So it seems like honestly, so it has got to be so relieving or helpful to know like it's
an experiment and you can switch back.
Yeah.
And now that we've had, we've had this happen in various parts of the organization a couple
of times now.
And again, it creates this permission structure for people to just try things.
And that obviously has like huge positive externalities when people are like less afraid
to go out on a limb and try something new.
I mean, again, being the first person to go from being an engineering manager back to
senior engineer, it's like super scary.
Like if you're the fifth one, like, yeah, that's a good point.
It kind of like snowballs, I guess.
Yeah.
It does feel like right now, like being, like creating an engineering culture where people
are excited to try experiments, even knowing they're not going to succeed.
Like that's like particularly today with AI, just so, so important.
Okay.
We went through Hex, life as a CTO.
How do you like to unwind at the end of the day?
What's your move?
I mean, we do a lot of the normal stuff. I also have a toddler, so not everything is unwinding.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Winding in different ways.
Once he's in bed, though, actually my husband and I have been, we've been playing through
together all of the Soulsborne games, which might be a little bit weird for an unwind session,
but it's like, it's a really good way to like, you know, release some tension, you know? We
like, I hadn't played them before, but like, I got started with Elden Ring, and then we like,
played all the way through Elden Ring. And then the rule is, when you die, you pass the controller.
So you get a little bit of a break. Like, you die, you pass it, and then you get another turn.
Do you have different specializations or jobs in Elden Ring, would you say? You and your husband?
Yeah, I will say he is much better at sort of like, learning the timing of the boss mechanics.
So he's typically like, he's gonna be a little better than that. I tend to be a little bit
better at the like, mobs, because I'm less reckless than he is. He just like, charges in
and just get like, totally annihilated. And I'm a little more strategic in how I like,
do the placement of the, yeah. My partner and I played a lot of Elden Ring, and I am very much
so that avoid the mobs, run away, like, learning that you don't have to fight everyone, didn't
realize that was an option in Elden Ring. Life changing, life changing. It's an option in real
life too. Yeah, I guess for the whole table of Elden Ring players, when you're playing with a
person, is this a collaborative, peaceful act, or? An act of violence. You know what I'm saying?
Well, we actually stopped playing real co-op games together because they got too intense.
And we were like, or it's just like, we've just different play styles. Again, like his is very
like, you know, just like rush straight at it. And mine's a little bit like, more sort of like,
careful exploratory. And so we were getting really mad at each other. Like we tried to play
Baldur's Gate co-op together and just like, that did not go well. And so I actually think that this
model works a lot better. Like one person is in control at any given time. I feel like that's a
hot tag. I love Baldur's Gate because split screen, you can almost have a co-adventure,
like, or completely different adventure. Yeah. Oh, you can split off. You're saying you took
the essence of playing separately, but within a cooperative game. Yeah, pretty much. You're like,
see ya. And then the screen just splits and you never reunite. Yeah. Sometimes. And then it's
like, oh no, I'm dying. Can you come help? Yeah. And then she'll pop in and have a good,
yeah, everybody for me. That's incredible. It's a good life.
Caitlin, really appreciate you coming on the test set. Thank you so much for having me. Yeah,
no, it's been great. I feel like so much to think about. I honestly, I hate to admit it,
but I feel like I have to. I hadn't learned about Context Studio, but it is going to live rent-free
in my head for the next probably all my life. We'll hook you up. I would love to, I mean,
always showing hex to people. I feel like, I don't actually, what you said about Context Studio
really kind of blew my mind because I do like a lot of software engineering on data tools,
but that strikes me as such a unique, maybe not totally unique problem across a lot of domains,
but for data people that need to like curate and stamp and endorse.
It's honestly like this moment in some ways is like a match made in heaven for data people for
this workflow, because this is the workflow that data teams have been doing forever, but it's just
been so painful and laborious for relatively little impact. Like if you think, or I mean,
obviously there's impact, but like the amount of impact you get out of like all of this labor
just sometimes doesn't feel worth it. Like, I don't know if you all remember, or I'm sure you
remember like when semantic models first kind of became a thing, we just didn't see a ton of
adoption of semantic models. And it wasn't because people didn't want them, it was just because it
was so painful and took so much time to build them out. And at the end it's like, okay, yeah,
only two people are going to be building your dashboards, right? And now today that's like
totally been inverted. Not only can you take constructs like semantic models and make them
available to everybody in the organization in a way they can use, but actually also you can do
the curation and you can do the governance much, much more easily with sort of agents yourself.
It is a pretty incredible that like it's both the cost has decreased dramatically and the impact
has increased dramatically. Like it's pretty unusual to get both of those at the same time.
It's pretty cool.
Yeah, totally. Yeah. So a lot to check out. Yeah. Can't recommend Hex enough. I feel like
also giving software engineers permission to like try things and fail, I think so relevant,
especially with AI where there's a lot of experimentation going on. And then I'm
putting in my pocket Elden Ring co-op strategies. I'm going to find peaceful ways to play with my
partner. But yeah, thanks so much for coming on. It's been so nice and been great having you.
Awesome. It's been fun. Yeah. Thank you so much.
The Test Set is a production of PositPBC, an open source and enterprise tooling data science
software company. This episode was produced in collaboration with creative studio Adji.
For more episodes, visit thetestset.co or find us on your favorite podcast platform.